RG 033, Works Progress Administration for Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
- Series 8. Ethnic Groups Survey, 1942-012
  - 26. Occupational distribution materials, 1938 (Box 74)
    - Occupation distribution – New Haven and Hartford (Box 74)
    - Occupation distribution of the ethnic groups of Hartford, New Haven, Waterbury, New Britain, Stamford, Bridgeport (Box 74)
    - Methodology for occupation distribution (Box 74)
    - Analysis of Connecticut occupational distributions: New Haven, Bridgeport, Stamford, Hartford, New Britain, Waterbury-Butts & Evans (Box 74)
    - Occupational distribution of the major ethnic groups in New Haven, Hartford, Waterbury, Bridgeport, New Britain, Stamford (Based upon a 3% sample of family names of each group taken from the city directories of 1937) (Box 74)
    - Analysis of a 5% sampling of the active files of the Connecticut State employment service (Box 74)
    - Directory addresses, etc. 3% samples (Box 75)
    - Hartford directory names, 1937 (Box 75)
    - Bridgeport directory names, 1867, 1890 (Box 75)
    - Bridgeport directory names, 1910 (Box 75)
    - Bridgeport directory names, 1917 (Box 75)
    - Bridgeport city directory names, 1918 (Box 75)
    - Bridgeport city directory names, 1937 (Box 75)
    - New Britain Directory Names, 1937 (Box 76)
    - New Britain Directory Names, 1910 (Box 76)
    - New Britain Directory Names, 1900 (Box 76)
    - New Britain Directory Names, 1885 (Box 76)
    - Alleged Russian names – New Britain (Box 76)
    - Superfluous New Britain names: Polish, Hungarian, Slovak, Ukrainian (Box 76)
    - New Haven directory names, 1890 (Box 76)
    - New Haven directory names, 1910 (Box 76)
    - New Haven directory names, 1918 (Box 76)
    - New Haven directory names, 1937 (Box 76)
    - Stamford city directory names, 1879-1880, 1885-1886 (Box 77)
    - Waterbury directory names (Box 77)
    - Directory names – Stamford directory, 1890 (Box 77)
    - Stamford directory names, 1910 (Box 77)
    - Stamford directory names, 1917 (Box 77)
    - Stamford directory names, 1937 (Box 77)
  - 27. New Haven post office nationality questionnaires, 1940 (Box 77)
    Forms giving name, sex and nationality.
    Grouped by nationality.
  - 28. Files on agriculture studies, 1937-1940 (Box 78)
    Drafts of monographs or proposed chapters on "Ethnic factors" in the Connecticut agricultural community, with working papers and reference materials.
    - New England agriculture (Kostolefsky) (Box 78)
    - Percentages of farmers (Box 78)
    - Agriculture (1880 – 1921) – abandoned farms, etc. (Box 78)
    - Connecticut agriculture before 1880 (Box 78)
    - Agricultural letters (Box 78)
    - Ethnic factors in Connecticut agriculture 5 - town survey (Kostolefsky) (Box 78)
    - Italians in agriculture (Box 78)
    - Agriculture in Connecticut (Box 78)
    - 5 sets of charts of ethnic groups of Connecticut farmers (Box 78)
    - 4 sets of tables – population by nativity for countries by minor civil divisions – 1930 (Box 78)
    - 1 set of tables of ethnic origins of Connecticut farmers in 1920 (Box 78)
    - 2 sets of tables of ethnic factors of Connecticut farmers by countries (Box 78)
    - 1 set of tables of farm info of 5 countries of Connecticut (Box 78)
    - 1st set of tables of cash income farm sales 1937 (Box 78)
    - 1st set of tables of town population of Connecticut with reference to nativity (Box 78)
    - 1st set of tables on ethic groups of farm & total population (Box 78)
    - Summary of New England agricultural statistics 1 set tables (Box 78)
    - Incomplete sets of 14th U.S. census, Connecticut agriculture (Box 78)
    - Inventory of crops and animals (Box 79)
    - Foreign born Italians (Box 79)
    - Foreign born Non-Italians (Box 79)
    - Native born of native parents (Box 79)
    - Native born of foreign parents non-Italians (Box 79)
    - Assessment records – all farmers Ellington, Connecticut all property – agriculture, 1937 (Box 79)
    - Assessment records – individual returns Ellington, Connecticut all property – names Aberle, H. to Zahornacky, S., 1937 (Box 79)
    - Assessment records – individual returns – Goshen, Connecticut, 1938 (Box 80)
    - 1938 assessment records – all farmers – Goshen, Connecticut real estate (Box 80)
    - Assessment records – individual returns – Lebanon, Connecticut all property, 1938 (Box 80)
    - Assessment records – individual returns – Lebanon, Connecticut – non-resident names, 1938 (Box 80)
    - Assessment records – all farmers – Lebanon, Connecticut all property, 1938 (Box 80)
    - 1938 assessment records – individual returns – Newtown, Connecticut all property; names – Allen, S. & T. to Jones, I.S. (Box 80)
    - Assessment records – all farmers – Newtown, Connecticut all property, 1938 (Box 80)
    - Assessment records – individual returns – Newtown, Connecticut all property, names – Kach, Michael to Zymbaluk, F., 1938 (Box 80)
    - Assessment records – individual returns – Newtown, Connecticut – all property, foreign names, 1938 (Box 80)
    - Old age assistance records names – Newtown, Connecticut ages 21-60, 1938 (Box 80)
    - Assessment Records – all farmers, North Haven, Connecticut – all property, 1938 (Box 80)
    - I. section III tables on choice of types of occupation (Box 81)
    - II. section V types of farming entered by each of the ethnic groups (Box 81)
    - III. section V types of farming entered by each of the ethnic groups work sheets (Box 81)
    - IV. section XII worksheets quality of farmland (Box 81)
    - V. section X worksheets standard of living (Box 81)
    - VII. work folder for North Haven (Box 81)
    - VIII. work folder for Goshen (Box 81)
    - IX. work folder for Canterbury (Box 81)
    - X. work folder for Lebanon (Box 81)
    - XI. work folder for Newtown (Box 81)
    - XII. work folder for Ellington (Box 82)
    - XIV. sheet A age statistics work sheets on identification and education (Box 82)
    - XV. sheets B-C-D-E-F-G, work sheets (Box 82)
    - XVI. sheets H & J work sheets (Box 82)
    - XVII. sheets K & L work sheets on organizational leisure time, hobby, and affiliations (Box 82)
    - XVIII. sheet M worksheets on problems (Box 82)
    - XIX. sheet N and O work sheets (Box 82)
    - XX. duplicate material five town survey (Box 82)
    - XXI. duplicate material (Box 82)
    - XXII. work sheets on North Haven survey 1939 (Box 82)
    - XXIV. bibliography (Box 82)
    - XXV. pomological society: history – bibliography (Box 82)
    - Agriculture – farm descriptions – biographies – Clifford (Box 83)
    - Bibliography on farm abandonment, etc (Box 83)
    - Agriculture (Box 83)
    - Agriculture – notes by M. Bishop (Box 83)
    - Notes taken by L. Fugazy (Box 83)
    - Agriculture – miscellaneous agricultural background material, economics, sociology, ethnology (Box 83)
    - Agriculture – copy for typist (Box 83)
    - Agriculture, outlines of research in rural subjects background material (Box 83)
    - Agriculture, Mr. Kostolefsky (Box 83)
    - Boston poultry show Vol I (Box 84)
    - Boston poultry show Vol II (Box 84)
    - History of the Boston poultry show 1839-1939 vol. 1 (Box 84)
    - A bibliography of newspapers and other periodicals published in Boston of special value in search of items on Boston poultry show (Box 84)
  - 29. Files on study of organizations, 1936-1940 (Box 85)
    Edited copy of papers on ethnic organizations, together with lists, working papers and related materials.
    - Ethnic organization lists (previously unfiled) part 1 (Box 85)
    - Ethnic organization lists (previously unfiled) part 2 (Box 85)
    - Mutual aid societies (Mittelstein), 1939 (Box 85)
    - Foreign community clubs, lodges, societies & organizations (Box 85)
    - Organizations – index – folders on societies, organizations, and clubs (Box 85)
    - Checko – Slovaks organizations II (Box 85)
    - Lithuanian organizations III (Box 85)
    - Canadian organization IV (Box 85)
    - Greek and Polish organizations V, VI (Box 85)
    - Irish organizations VIII (Box 85)
    - Italian & Jewish organizations IX & X (Box 85)
    - Russian and Hungarian organizations XI & XII (Box 85)
    - Norwegian, Danish & British American organizations XIV, XV, XVI (Box 85)
    - English, Scotch, and Yankee organizations XIX & XX (Box 85)
    - Covers of empty folders of ethnic organizations (Box 85)
    - Organizations: Hartford, New Britain, Bridgeport, Waterbury, New Haven, Stamford (Box 86)
    - Ukrainian organizations of Connecticut (Box 86)
    - Miscellaneous data on Connecticut organizations (Box 86)
    - Organizations in Bridgeport: Slovak, Norwegians, English, Russian (Box 86)
    - Summaries of organizations (Box 86)
    - Organizations, clubs, societies (Box 86)
    - Ethnic distribution of organizations (Box 86)
    - Organizations in New Haven (Box 86)
    - Organizations, New Haven and Hartford (Box 86)
    - Organizations in New Britain (Box 86)
    - Organizations in Waterbury (Box 86)
    - Armenian organizations and names (Box 87)
    - Irish organizations of Connecticut (Box 87)
    - French-Canadian organizations of Connecticut (Box 87)
    - German organizations of Connecticut (Box 87)
    - Greek organizations of Connecticut (Box 87)
    - Irish organizations-Hartford manuals and pamphlets (Box 87)
    - Italian organizations of Connecticut (Box 88)
    - Italian organizations (Box 88)
    - Italian organizations (Box 88)
    - Italian organizations of New Haven (Box 88)
    - Italian organizations of New Haven-newspaper clippings (Box 88)
    - Jewish organizations of New Haven (Box 89)
    - Hartford Jewish organizations of New Haven (mutual aid) (Box 89)
    - Italian organizations of New Haven (Box 89)
    - Italian organizations of New Haven (Box 89)
    - Ethnic group, the Jews (Box 90)
    - New Britain – Ukrainians of New Britain (Box 90)
    - Modern Stamford – ethnic studies – Jews – Swedes – Russians – Greeks (Box 90)
    - Jewish organizations of Hartford (Box 90)
    - Jewish organizations of Hartford (social & cultural societies) (Box 90)
    - Lithuanian, Magyar & Russian organizations of Connecticut (Box 90)
    - Negro organizations (Box 90)
    - Ethnic distributions of organizations in Connecticut (Box 91)
    - Yankee group interviews by John P. Kilgore (corrected original copies) (Box 91)
    - Polish organizations of Connecticut (Box 91)
    - Portuguese of Connecticut: organizations, living conditions, etc. (Box 91)
    - Swedish organizations of Connecticut: New Haven & Hartford (Box 91)
  - 30. Reports of interviews (“Biographies”), 1937-1940 (Box 92)
    Reports of detailed interviews with members of ethnic groups concerning their history, status, opinions about their life and place in the community, etc.
    - French-Canadians of Bridgeport (Box 92)
    - Life histories – Jews – Hartford (Box 92)
    - Life histories – Jews – Hartford (Box 92)
    - Life histories – Jews – Hartford (Box 92)
    - Biographies by Rahel Mittelstien – December 7, 1939 (Box 92)
    - Jewish biographies – New Haven (Box 92)
    - Jewish biographies by Jason Kohn (mostly New Haven) (Box 92)
    - Jews of Hartford – biographies (Morton Tonken) (Box 92)
    - Lithuanians in Waterbury (Box 92)
    - Poles of New Britain (Box 92)
    - Biographies of the Swedes of New Haven (Box 93)
    - Swedes of Bridgeport (Box 93)
    - Slovaks of Bridgeport (Box 93)
    - Swedes (life histories) (Box 93)
    - Portuguese – Manuel Oliveira (Clark) (Box 93)
    - Portuguese survey (Robertson) (Box 93)
    - Portuguese survey – McKenna (Box 93)
    - Portuguese survey – Manuel Chaves (McKenna) (Box 93)
    - Abstract – background – Portuguese of Hartford (Clark) (Box 93)
    - Previously unfiled – speech by E. A. Buitt (Box 94)
    - Interviews: ethnic studies – list of persons interviewed on ethnic survey (Box 94)
    - Yankee interviews (Box 94)
    - Yankee interviews – J. Kilgore (Part 2) (Box 94)
    - Yankee interviews – J. Kilgore (Part 1) (Box 94)
    - Yankee interviews – J. Kilgore (Part 3) (Box 94)
    - Stamford – miscellaneous biographies (Box 95)
    - Henry Gogay (Box 95)
    - Biographies Yankees – Thomaston, Connecticut (Box 95)
    - Biographies by Francis Donovan (Box 95)
    - Hartford – Yankee biographies (Box 95)
    - Life histories (Box 95)
  - 31. Materials on ethnic factors in industry, trade and commerce, 1937-1940 (Box 96)
    Drafts, working papers, correspondence and reports dealing with the ethnic make-up of industries, trades, professions, individual firms and institutions, with unemployment and the problems of youth, and related subjects.
    - Industry – domestic workers – Hartford and New Haven (Box 96)
    - Trade jargon – submitted to regional – (Youngs) (Box 96)
    - Connecticut Mutual Life Ins. Co. – Hartford (Box 96)
    - Studies of neighborhoods (Box 96)
    - Industry – neighborhood studies (Box 96)
    - Previously unfiled (Box 96)
    - Trade and commerce (Box 96)
    - Industries of Connecticut (Box 96)
    - Industry – New Haven (Box 96)
    - Trade & Commerce – Finished essay (Evans) (Box 96)
    - Industry – unemployment & problems of youth (Box 96)
    - (Evans) – trade & commerce – tables dealing with material already written (Box 96)
    - Business firms in New Haven from 1937 directory (Box 96)
    - Mary Lent (Box 96)
    - Dept of Labor wages & hours of work in the Lock & Wood Screw Industries (Lenk) (previously unfiled) (Box 96)
    - Interviews with older employees of Seth Thomas Clock Co. (Box 96)
    - Trade & commerce – Evans (Box 96)
    - New Britain industries (Box 96)
    - Katz – businesses to be examined (previously unlabeled) (Box 96)
    - Notes & information on fisheries (Box 97A)
    - Thomaston industrial questionnaires (Box 97A)
    - Bridgeport industrial questionnaires (Box 97A)
    - Industrial distribution – work sheets (Box 97A)
    - Industry miscellaneous (Box 97A)
    - Survey of business establishments in Connecticut (Box 97A)
    - Questionnaires for interviewing industrial workers of New Britain, Connecticut (Box 97A)
    - Industry – Waterbury (Box 97A)
    - Six professions in six Connecticut cities (Box 97B)
    - Bridgeport, Connecticut – statistics of industrial workers – 52 cases (males & females) (Box 97B)
    - Notes & data on industry at present (Box 97B)
    - Oyster industry in Connecticut – L. R. Fugazy (Box 97B)
    - New Britain, Connecticut statistics on industrial workers – 22 cases (Box 97B)
    - Thomaston, Connecticut – statistics on Indus trial workers – 30 cases (all males) (Box 97B)
  - 32. Materials on ethnic factors in cultural life, 1937-1940 (Box 98)
    Drafts, working papers and reference materials on art, music and the theatre in Connecticut.
    - Hartford art (Box 98)
    - Art & science (Box 98)
    - New Haven drama tournament groups – Earle, 1940 (Box 98)
    - Music (Box 98)
    - Art in Connecticut (Box 98)
    - Literature & art – Stamford & case memorial library (Box 98)
    - Theatres in Connecticut (McKenna) (Box 98)
    - Art & music & drama correspondence (Box 98)
    - Music, drama, art organization program (Box 98)
    - New Haven music (Box 99)
    - Summer Theatre in Connecticut (Box 99)
    - Music & art societies & summer theatre (Box 99)
    - Summer theatre programs (Box 99)
    - Manuscript – drama music – Dr. Albert (Box 99)
    - Drama – newspaper clippings, pamphlets, etc. (Box 99)
    - Art and science (Young & Gottlieb) (Box 99)
    - Art and science in Connecticut (Box 99)
    - Music in Connecticut (biographies & membership lists) (Box 99)
  - 33. Materials on ethnic factors in education, 1937-40 (Box 100)
    Drafts and working papers on ethnic factors in Connecticut education.
    - Education in Connecticut (copy 3) by Butts – Youngs (Box 100)
    - Education in Connecticut (Butts – Youngs) part IV, chapter 1 (Box 100)
    - Education – manuscript copy (Box 100)
    - Education – Connecticut State College (degrees & diplomas) (Box 100)
    - Teachers colleges – educational statistics (Box 100)
    - Education – grammar, high & parochial schools in 169 towns (Box 100)
    - Parochial schools (duplicate) (Box 100)
    - Parochial schools (Box 100)
    - List of publications (Box 100)
    - List of students (Box 100)
    - Lists of teachers, principals, and boards of education (Box 100)
    - Biographies of schools principals – Darien, Derby, Norwalk, Putnam, Stamford, Wallingford, Waterbury, Windham, Meriden, Deep River, New Haven, Newington (Box 100)
    - Parochial schools (Box 100)
    - Biographies of school principals – New Haven (Box 100)
    - Education (general) New Haven, New Britain, Hartford & Bridgeport (Box 101)
    - Education – Bridgeport – state trade schools (Box 101)
    - Education – Bridgeport (Box 101)
    - Education – Bridgeport, New Britain, etc (Box 101)
    - Education – Bridgeport – Central High School (Box 101)
    - Bridgeport community studies – school statistics (Box 101)
    - Education – Bridgeport – state trade schools (Box 101)
    - Education – Hartford (Box 101)
    - Education – New Haven (Box 101)
    - Education – Milford (Box 101)
    - Education – New Haven public schools (Box 101)
    - Interviews with principals of public schools in New Haven (Box 101)
  - 34. Completed studies, 1940-1941 (Box 102)
    - Outline for a study of the Jews (Box 102)
    - History of Stamford Jewish community – field copy (Box 102)
    - Modern Stamford – correspondence (Box 102)
    - Contemporary Connecticut – economic & social structure (Box 102)
    - Social maladjustment in Connecticut (Box 102)
  - 35. Miscellaneous drafts, working papers and reference materials, 1936-1941 (Box 103)
    - Religion – church statistics (Box 103)
    - Sunday schools & Jewish education (Box 103)
    - Sunday schools – New Haven (Box 103)
    - “Incomplete work” (Box 103)
    - Foreign press in Connecticut (Box 103)
    - Foreign language newspapers (Box 103)
    - Foreign language press – Groboski (Box 103)
    - Hartfonder Stadt – Bote – German (Katz) (Box 103)
    - Churches of New Haven (Box 103)
    - Churches (Box 103)
    - Churches & affiliated institutions – New Haven, Hartford, Waterbury, Bridgeport, New Britain (Box 103)
    - Foreign language newspapers (Box 103)
    - Population – files used in population study (Box 104)
    - Portuguese of Connecticut – by Youngs (Box 104)
    - The Portuguese by Dr. Rodnick (Box 104)
    - Portuguese: outline (Box 104)
    - Percentage of each ethnic group in the total population of Connecticut (Box 104)
    - Population statistics – data – used (Box 104)
    - Ethnic grouping of officers & members of the House of Representatives by counters 1776, 1780, 1820, 1840, 1867, 1890, 1910, 1918, 1937 (Box 104)
    - Ethnic composition of the National Guard – New Haven (Box 104)
    - Ethnic origin of New Haven city employees (Box 104)
    - Connecticut National Guard – 169th infantry regiment, Hartford district (Box 104)
    - 13th, 14th & 15th U.S. census – Youngs (Box 104)
    - Colonial Connecticut – a homogenous commonwealth (part 3 – chapter 1) (Box 105)
    - Miscellaneous essays & data (Box 105)
    - Famous Americans of foreign stock – field copy (Box 105)
    - Juvenile delinquency – Jack H. Katz (Box 105)
    - Mental disease statistics (notes) (Box 105)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 105)
    - Ethnography – foreigners in New Haven (Box 105)
    - Ethnic – Stamford (Box 105)
    - (Previously unlabeled) Italian votes in New Haven (Box 105)
    - Contents of the various volumes of the biblioteca delle tradizion, poplar, sialliane by Dr. G Pitre (Box 105)
    - Clubs, org. – Robertson (Box 105)
    - Ethnic studies by New Britain workers (Box 105)
  - 36. Newspaper excerpts on ethnic matter, 1915-1940 (Box 106)
    Summaries and transcriptions of material from leading Connecticut newspapers pertaining to ethnic groups or individuals and related matters.
    - Newspaper excerpts – Groups I. Jews, Poles, Italians, etc (Box 106)
    - Newspaper excerpts II, economic life (Box 106)
    - Newspaper excerpts II, immigration (Box 106)
    - Newspaper excerpts, religion (Box 106)
    - Newspaper excerpts II, social life (Box 106)
    - Newspaper excerpts II, labor (Box 106)
    - Newspaper excerpts II, politics (Box 106)
    - New Britain Record – ethnic studies (Box 107)
    - Hartford Courant – ethnic studies (Box 107)
    - Hartford Times – ethnic studies (Box 107)
    - Hartford Daily Courant – ethnic studies (Box 107)
    - Journal Courier New Haven – ethnic studies (Box 107)
    - Milford Citizen – ethnic studies (Box 107)
    - New Haven Palladium – ethnic studies (Box 107)
    - Daily Morning Courier New Haven – ethnic studies (Box 107)
    - New Britain Record – tabulation of articles & notes on ethnic groups of New Britain (Box 107)
    - New Haven Sunday Register (Box 108)
    - New Haven Register (Box 108)
    - New Haven Times Leader (Box 108)
    - New Haven Union – ethnic studies (Box 108)
    - Newspapers excerpts – criminal cases (Box 108)
    - Newspaper excerpts – miscellaneous (Box 108)
  - 37. Bridgeport office file, 1936-1940 (Box 109)
    Work files, drafts of copy and other related materials, often essentially duplicated in central office files.
    - Hungarians – Norwalk (work files) – H. Lee Conner (Box 109)
    - Hungarians – Norwalk (edited copy) – H. Lee Conner (Box 109)
    - Racial survey by town – Sherman, New Fairfield, Fairfield – Harold Drews (Box 109)
    - Racial survey by town – Bridgeport, Fairfield – Jeanette Winkel (Box 109)
    - Racial survey by town – Stamford, Bethel – Rhonda Cameron (Box 109)
    - Poles - Stamford - Rhonda Cameron (Box 109)
    - Darien & New Canaan – H. Lee Conner (Box 109)
    - Norwalk, Westport – C.L. Dennis (Box 109)
    - Germans – Bridgeport – Harold Drews (Box 109)
    - Wilton, Weston, Redding – T. O’Coner Sloane, 3rd (Box 109)
    - Greenwich & Brookfield – Frank Vanderhoof (Box 109)
    - Connecticut folklore – Frank Vanderhoof (Box 109)
    - English – Bridgeport – B. Vincent Healy (Box 109)
    - Norwegians – Bridgeport – Jeanette Winkel (Box 109)
    - Greeks – Bridgeport – Jeanette Winkel (Box 109)
    - Bridgeport – C. L. Dennis (Box 109)
    - Great Russians – Bridgeport (work file) – William J. Becker (Box 110)
    - Hungarians – Norwalk (work file) – H. Lee Conner 1 (Box 110)
    - Hungarians – Norwalk (work file) – H. Lee Conner 2 (Box 110)
    - French – Bissonette (Box 110)
    - Greeks (Stamford) – (work file) – Rhoda Cameron (Box 110)
    - Poles – Stamford (work file) – Henry Coles (Box 110)
    - Czecho-slovak – Bridgeport (work file) – Louise E. Doyle (Box 110)
    - Great Russians – Bridgeport, Stratford (work file) – Mary Gaffney (Box 110)
    - Norwegians – Bridgeport (work file) – Vincent B. Healy (Box 110)
    - Lithuanians – Bridgeport (work file) – Genevieve McGrath (Box 110)
    - Ethnic survey – Marshall V. Rourke (Box 110)
    - Lithuanians – Bridgeport (work file) – Joseph Skubas (Box 110)
    - Armenians – Bridgeport (work file) – Marjorie Stuart (Box 110)
    - List of organizations (work file) – Mabel Sheehan (Box 110)
    - English/Scotch – Bridgeport (work file) – Marjorie Stuart (Box 110)
    - Great Russians (edited) – William J. Becker (Box 111)
    - Greeks & Poles - Stamford – Rhoda Cameron (Box 111)
    - Poles – Stamford (edited) – Henry Coles (Box 111)
    - Hungarians – Norwalk – Conner, H. Lee (edited) (Box 111)
    - Czecho-slovaks – Bridgeport (edited) – Louise E. Doyle (Box 111)
    - Great Russians – Bridgeport, Stratford (edited) – Mary Gaffney (Box 111)
    - Norwegians – Bridgeport – Vincent B. Healy (Box 111)
    - Lithuanians – Bridgeport (edited) – Genevieve McGrath (Box 111)
    - Lithuanians – Bridgeport (edited) – Joseph Skubas (Box 111)
    - List of organizations (edited copy) – Mabel Sheehan (Box 111)
    - Armenians – Bridgeport (edited) – Marjorie Stuart (Box 111)